I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Saku!
What's up, Koyuki?
You're excited this morning.
It's been decided! The album!
You mean-?
Yup! Dying Breed's releasing a new album!
Eh?!
They're releasing their first single!
I've got to buy it ASAP!
Yeah, then can you loan it to me?
Sure thing.
Did you see last night's Best UK?
Yeah, it was excellent!
-His white shirt and yellow tie!
-That guy was so cool!
Yeah!
"Eve of the Live Show"
Let's see...For the
200m individual medley...
Yes. I nominate Yukio Tanaka.
Huh? Tanaka-kun?
Sensei! This swim meet commemorates
our school's 40th anniversary.
For our class's honor, we should
aspire to our utmost formation.
Yeah, right.
That sounds incredibly lame.
For sure...What a joke.
But, Tanaka-kun...
Is it all right?
Well...
He's fine with it.
Tanaka-kun's been getting
expert lessons from some Saito creep.
Who the heck is that?!
Never heard of 'im!
Then everyone, it's decided, okay?
Umm, 100m Backstroke, Yukio Tanaka.
50m Butterfly, Yukio Tanaka.
200m Individual Medley,
Yukio Tanaka. 50m-
-This is exciting!
-Yeah!
Typhoon 24! 24-7! 24 hours straight!
We're gonna rush at you!
Gonna send you flyin'!
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
you'll feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
-He scratches like a DJ!
-You just have to Stage Dive or Die
-Ryusuke-kun's incredible!
-Mind blower, a shower of sweat
-Definitely influenced by
Rage Against the Machine's Tom Morello.
-Run towards a new world, my life
-Definitely influenced by
Rage Against the Machine's Tom Morello.
-Run towards a new world, my life
-Definitely influenced by
Rage Against the Machine's Tom Morello.
-Those who seek it will be rewarded
-Ryusuke-kun's got
a really broad background...
-Pass the hot shot,
-Ryusuke-kun's got
a really broad background...
-Pass the hot shot,
-Ryusuke-kun's got
a really broad background...
-keep on coming, come on!
-Ryusuke-kun's got
a really broad background...
-Blow your mind
-Hey, Saku, you say something?
-Squeeze your sweat yeah
-Chiba-kun's vocals are a bit uneven,
-Blow your mind
-Squeeze your sweat
-but he's got that quality
that draws people in.
-Squeeze your sweat
-but he's got that quality
that draws people in.
-Find the way you are,
-Yeah.
-Spice of your life
-Just listening to him really pumps you up!
-Heavy beat, hey come on people
Find the way you are,
spice of your life
-And Taira-kun's bass...
-Heavy beat, hey come on people yeah
-The bass?
-Take your spice yeah
-He's awesome!
-I didn't think a Japanese guy
could play such a funky bass...
-Take your spice yeah
-I didn't think a Japanese guy
could play such a funky bass...
-Find my wife
And the drums...
...are a bit lacking.
-Super hot me, set me afire
-Frankly, I think it's holding them back.
-Huh, what did you say?
-Out of this world, this perfect stage
Spice up my flight
I'm not holding back, check it out
Ryusuke-kun's guys
are getting pretty good.
You think? Bands like this
are a dime a dozen in Japan.
Looks like a tough sell to
promote a band out of this joint.
Squeeze your sweat yeah
Blow your mind
What, I fronted the studio fees last time.
The nerve of you!
You owe me 60,000 yen!
By the way, what are we going to do
about our van's safety check?
I'm broke already this month.
I'm broke too!
Hey, hey, we can't break up
just 'cause we're broke.
Looks like we need more customers
to keep things going.
That may be the toughest thing to do.
-Taira-kun...
-Huh?
Where can we find
some money lying around?
I'm outta here.
Oh, Togo-kun. I'm counting on you
to design our next flyer!
Yeah. Well, I've got to go drop her off.
Seems Beck is trapped in a
Mobius strip of the unpopular bands.
Mobius strip? What do you mean?
This is bad!
What's the matter?
Hey, don't scare us.
T-t-that Tanaka creep...
Hey, you! What a crappy start!
Need to raise the pitch, you idiot!
Your left hand's not
grabbing the water, fool!
Your timing is way off!
-Go for it!
-Go!
Moron! Don't take a breath
right after the turn!
Hey! Your kicking is getting weak!
Kick like your life depends on it!
-All right!
-He did it!
Hey, isn't Tanaka-kun incredible?!
He's seriously awesome!
The results are in. In first place
is grade 9-D, Kohei Takahashi.
Second place, Grade 9-A, Yukio Tanaka.
Third place, Grade 9-B, Kazuo Watanabe.
We'll shame him in the 100m backstroke.
We'll show him what the
swim school training is made of!
We're going to crush Tanaka!
What was that touch earlier?!
You had one stroke too many!
Saito-san, where're we going?
Practice your start in the 25m pool!
Until time's up!
I'm sorry...I'm...cramping...already...
Hey...Hey! Koyuki!
Koyuki! Ko-Koyuki-kun?
You're incredible, Koyuki!
I was cheering for you
the whole time from the stands.
I'll help you stretch.
Koyuki, lie on your stomach.
Okay...
Koyuki, you were great!
By the way, I heard that
Togo-kun might quit the band.
Huh? But, why?
He's getting a lot of pressure
from his parents and his girlfriend.
Seems they want him to help out
with the family business.
Yeah?
That's why he hasn't been
coming to practice lately.
Okay, face forward.
Then what's going
to happen with the drums?
Don't know.
This might be the end of Beck.
It's tough, you know, turning professional.
All right, stretching completed!
Thanks!
I'll swim my best!
My stretching isn't free!
That'll be 10,500 yen, tax inclusive!
What?!
Hey, let's do that, if Koyuki loses!
But, if he does win, I'd like
to see Maho-chan give him a reward.
Let's make a wager!
It'll raise his motivation level!
But...
Okay!
If Koyuki wins this tournament,
I'll do whatever he asks.
Eh?! Maho...
On your mark, get set...
Swim like your life depends on it!
Koyuki!
Tanaka-kun! Go for it!
Tanaka! Come on!
Wow...
Koyuki! You'll be disgraced
if you lose!
Go get 'em!
Tanaka-kun!
-Go for it!
-Tanaka-kun!
Hey, what're you going
to do about Tanaka?
Damn, that Tanaka!
Koyuki!
First place is Grade 9-A, Yukio Tanaka!
His time's not bad.
Damn.
Hey, what're we going to do?
This doesn't look good.
Hey, Hyodo!
"Health Room"
Thank you very much.
Well, when you get home,
put an ice pack on it.
Right.
Koyuki!
That was incredible!
Our class won the tournament
because you came in first place!
I made...first place?
Koyuki, you made first place!
I...I've got to thank Saito-san.
-He's still at the pool.
-Yeah.
Isn't that...Momoko-sensei?
That's right.
Seems she asked him to teach her.
I hope things go well between those two.
-It seems interesting.
-Yeah, I guess.
Oh, Togo-san!
Take care, Koyuki.
Togo-san...
Yeah...can't be helped.
He's quitting the band to help out
with his family's business.
Ryusuke-kun...
Well, it's a tough world.
To think someone good like
Togo-san would be quitting...
Isn't it time for your rehearsal-
Stupid! How can we rehearse
without a drummer?
I guess I could spend the day
re-reading "Happy Sangokushi."
Let's see...How far did I get again?
Powerful and straightforward...
And with feeling.
Saku's on the drums?!
Saku...
How long have you been
playing the drums?
Since I was seven, after my older brother.
Oh yeah? Are you from a musical family?
No, not at all.
My brother's into baseball now.
I see.
I'm completely self-taught,
so I'm not very confident.
Saku...
Yo!
You're late, Chiba!
Yeah, I wanted Togo-kun to reconsider.
So I went to talk to him.
And?
Not gonna happen.
Well, can't be helped.
Why are you sitting there?
What?! Those two?!
Yeah, I want to make Koyuki and Saku
part of our support members.
But they're only in intermediate school.
Saku might be okay,
but Koyuki's nowhere near our level.
After hearing Saku's drums today,
I wanted to take a gamble on them.
Gamble? With Togo gone,
this whole band could go under.
Technical skill alone
doesn't make a band.
What's important...is the "chemistry."
Ryusuke-kun mentioned "chemistry."
"Chemistry"-like a chemical reaction?
I can just see a huge explosion!
Ka-boom!
You guys haven't heard?
We're performing live a week from now?
But we haven't practiced long...
It's an event with some
serious attendance.
We're gonna wow the crowd and
take the other bands' customers!
-Oh...
So we're gonna practice extra hard,
starting tomorrow.
Hey, Chiba-kun! Pay up, won't you?
Huh? Don't got none.
Check it out!
Yeah!
Hey! You're off beat!
What, you want me to carry this?!
Ouch...
Hey, are you all right?
I think I'm just a bit nervous.
Hey, are you getting nervous
about carrying in the equipment?
Come on, everyone gets nervous
before playing a gig.
Even Jimi Hendrix, Jimmy Page,
Flea, Tom Morello...
Everyone's the same.
But, I heard that the Stones
play billiards before playing live...
They do that to ease the tension.
Saku...Wanna go shoot some pool?
Huh? What about the rehearsal?
The bands that were rehearsing
before us were all really good.
Okay, Beck! It's your turn.
During rehearsal,
we check the sound balance.
First we do the drums,
and my vocals get done last.
Oh well, I've got to do my very best now.
The guitar, please. 15 minutes left.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
-This is Okute-san of Le Mans Porche!
-We're this week's musicians!
"Next Episode"
-This is Okute-san of Le Mans Porche!
-We're this week's musicians!
"Next Episode"
Go, Le Mans Porche! Nice to meet you!